

# **Contacts**

(+244) 933 57 05 22 ray.developper@gmail.com

# Social media

- **ு** typerguy
- typerrguy
- in Raimundo Tony



# Raimundo Tony

# Front-end developer



#### Resume

I'm an oriented-result frontend developer, focused in delivering high-quality Front-end solutions (I'm working to be Full-Stack developer). I have been working since 2016 as a frontend developer, developing and deploying institutional websites with more than 1000 visits per day and internal applications for financial and management purposes. My experience has always been in Angolan public companies.

# **Experience**

2019-Present

# Frontend Developer

SIAC- Angola

- Responsible for desing and developing the Frontend of all Internal Software using Reactjs
- I have also developed roles of Product Owner and Project Manager in the absence of the Head of Technology Department

2018-2019

# Frontend Instructor (React JS)

Bukapp - Education Sturtup

 Teach Reactjs, Nextjs, Typescript, Javascript, Tailwind, & Styled-Components

2016-2018

#### **Android Developer**

Ministry of Public Administration, Labor and Social Security - MAPTSS

 Android development with Java, Android Studdio, XML and Firebase and Scrum+Kamban

#### **Education**

2018-2024

## **Catholic University of Angola**

Computer Science and engineering

2015-2017

Telecommunications Institute

Infromatics & Computers

# **Adress**

São João Nº 4, Ngola-Kiluanji, Cazenga, Luanda, Angola

# reference contacts

#### Mário Inácio

- minacio@siac.gv.ao
- SIAC- Vice director.

#### **Evaristo Tone**

- evaristo.tone@gmail.com
- TSCO CEO

#### Augusto Firmino

- augusto@inokri.com
- SóciaApp CEO



# **Skills & Tools**

SASS
LESS
Reactjs
NextJs
Styled-Components
Redux
TailWind
Bootstrap
ChakraUI

PostgreSQL
MongoDB
MySQL
Firebase
Figma
AdobeXD
Jira
Trello
Java
C & c++

# language

# Portuguese Pt-pt

Nativo

Node

**TypeScript** 

**HTML** 

JS

## **English**

Intermadiate

## **Soft Skills**

Good Comunication
Problem Solving
Liedership
Critical Thinking
Commitment
Sustainable thinking

Team Work
Colaboration
Open to share

#### More about me

I already won the Microsoft imagine Cup contest in my country.

I share content about reactjs, js and typscript on my social networks

I win the Angolan math olympics of secundary & univesity level

I also organized lectures on Human Development and Leadership in Africa With Entrepreneurs

I was part of the list of the 10 most creative young people in Angola, chosen by Empresa Nacional Tigra. Because of my Micro Insurance Stutup for Low Income People in Southern Africa